Why did you stop?
Come on!
Huh?
If that's all you can do
don't bother next time
I'll go find someone else
You got it?
Almost done
James!
James! You motherfucker!
Bitch, where are you?
Fucking hell!
Where's James?
I said where the fuck is James?
Can't you hear it?
Almost done. Bitch!
I let you two fuck with our clients,
not with each other.
I said stop!
Fuck off!
Are you dogs, fuckers?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Bitch!
You wanna die, whore?
You're the whore!
You took my shit, didn't you?
What shit?
I can't hold it anymore.
I said stop! Motherfucker!
Fuck you! Bitch!
I couldn't finish my drug cost last time
because of you.
Did you tell James to take my shit?
What shit are you talking about?
Don't fucking lie.
Are you high on diet pills?
What fucking lie!
If you got a problem, sort it out with him.
You do it, sell it by yourselves.
What's it got to do with me?
It fucking does!
It passed you guys those drugs here.
So it fucking does!
You fucking get out now!
No!
Why the fuck are you still here?
I said get out!
You and I gotta talk!
If not, no client today!
Bitch! I'm working!
You mind your own shit!
You're working with my guy!
Your guy? Did you sign a contract?
You wanna take this to the Big Boss?
Do you?
Are you making Big boss threatening me?
Not just threatening,
but I fucking mean it!
Or you wanna fight with me?
Who the fuck wanna fight (fuck) you?
With lips so red like dog's period.
Ever looked at yourself in the mirror?
You put your mom's period on your lips?
Come on!
I'm fucking coming!
Why did you stop?
Why the fuck did you stop!
Hit me.
Come on! Hit me!
Are you sure?
You brought this on yourself.
Shit!
Damn!
Fucking hell!
Come on!
Enough!
I said enough!
Let go of me!
I said stop! You bitch!
Are you gonna stop?
No!
Are you gonna shoot me?
Cuz you won't stop.
You side with him.
And blame it on me.
Tell her.
About what we discussed.
Shut up!
Tell her! Tell her now!
You're gonna shut up?
You have no guts?
Want me to tell her?
Will you shut up, motherfucker?
Spit it out!
Don't push me.
Don't fucking push me.
What do you want?
You want me to take the blame?
Do you?
I gotta take this to the Big Boss.
And if you two aren't guilty,
then someone must be punished.
You bitch!
Stand up!
Smile
Smile... Smile
Smile!
Come here!
I said come here!
Strip.
Strip!
Prick!
Who told you to put it on?
Come on!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm the one who should ask you,
not the other way around.
What do you want from me?
What would I get from someone like you?
Why are you trying to
make her misunderstand me?
You got a brain. Go figure.
About what you asked me last night,
were you being serious or just kidding?
Bitch!
How is it?
Who are you talking about?
Not you.
I had to do it.
You had to do it, or you want to do it?
Of course I had to.
Unless you want this to end with you.
Do you know what I'm thinking right now?
Do you want to have it more?
Wait here. I'll be right back.
How many cuts?
A lot.
Smartass!
Then what should I answer?
Go get it done!
What the fuck are you looking at? Go!
That's enough.
Enough!
What's the matter?
You see we're having problems.
Let's do it next time.
What the fuck is wrong?
Jealous?
I have the right to be?
Nobody has the right to
feel anything for anybody.
We're just taking our responsibilities.
That's it.
Whore!
You can go now.
I might have clients in the afternoon.
Where are you going?
Get some food.
Shit!
Ouch! What the fuck is wrong with you?
What the fuck do you want?
Why don't you sit with me?
I'm sitting with you now.
Bored?
Of you?
Of yourself.
You know something?
If not for Big Boss,
I'll still be washing
the dishes over there.
Where?
I asked him if I could be
a child seat drink.
He wouldn't let me.
You wanna be a whore?
You think I'm pretty?
I think you've made the right choice.
It's me who still hasn't gone anywhere.
Try ignoring your personal feelings.
I am bewildered.
Don't let it take over you.
How was last night?
Mac didn't use it.
But he saw me doing it. Fucking crazy.
So what?
He helps us make money.
And another thing is
we're working as a team.
Actually, what do you want to tell me?
Don't imagine what hasn't really happened.
And don't put your thoughts
into someone else's.
You still love him, don't you.
Are you asking me?
Or just questioning yourself?
I don't know what you said.
But what I know is,
You always try to pick on him.
For what?
This kind of job has
taught me to fool others.
But you've gone further than I have.
Because you've fooled yourself.
Don't try to drag me into your world.
If you don't have me,
Your life will be more difficult.
I'm feeling like trying.
You have the guts?
Wanna see me try?
Sit down.
I said sit down.
Sit down!
Sit, prick!
I let you use this gun only when necessary.
You must use it only when you have to.
Otherwise, never bring it out.
And never point it at my face again.
Ever thought about
how you would live without me?
And you've ever thought
Better get going.
We have lots to do.
What the fuck are you looking at?
Move!
I said move!
Fucking hell!
What the fuck are you looking at?
You're bitch, did I kill your dad?
Cocksucker!
Holy shit!
You're here by yourself?
Yes
How long have you been here?
A while
How about you?
Just got here.
Where are you from?
Far.
In the city.
Have you eaten anything?
You're gonna treat me?
I can.
Anything to eat around here?
Yes.
Candy.
Toys.
Everything.
Wanna try?
Interesting.
What are you looking for?
Someone.
Who?
Do you know Mac?
Of course.
Why did you ask?
Wanna see him?
No.
I'm here to see the other guy.
Mac is around here, right?
This place is kinda strange.
Dark alleys.
But when you come upstairs,
There's an outdoor space.
Bright.
Ever get scared?
Who exactly are you here to see?
You haven't told me
if you're scared or not.
You want me to scared of what?
What are you usually scared of?
You're PlayBoy, right?
Why do you know my name?
You're famous, aren't you?
Not many people know me.
Why not?
I'm not that important.
Why would they want to know me?
Or perhaps you don't allow them
to get to know you.
I want to know only who I want to know.
For those I don't want to know,
I only see them as strangers.
Why do you like having sex with strangers?
Maybe because I don't want to know them.
You're handsome.
Aren't you boyfriend jealous?
Would anyone with a boyfriend
stay in this kind of place?
How about you? Where's your boyfriend?
Why would you want to know?
Good point.
Why would I want to know?
It's amazing that
there're people who would
come all the way here.
There's just one type of people
who would come here.
Who?
Strangers.
Actually,
No one wants to come around here.
How come?
Dirty I guess.
Only dust.
There's no rain for ages.
Hot
And you like it?
Yeah, kind of.
I like sunlight,
open space.
I like it when people see me,
The way I see them.
How about you?
Ever had the same feelings?
Yeah.
But I feel everything
In the opposite way.
You already know what you have to do?
Where're the toys?
Keep this way.
When you see the construtec zone,
then turn left.
And you will find.
Your toy is waiting for you
on the top of the building.
Ought to go with you?
Special services?
No, it's not. Just my responsibility.
Sound like I'm being enforced.
So, I will see you in two hours.
Make it extreme! Just do not lost your way.
So, what are you gonna do with that Boy?
What are you doing?
You're making me worried.
This place is dark
and dirty.
Not suitable for someone like you.
Let's find something to do outside.
But it's more interesting in here.
But I don't want to do it here.
Why not? Afraid?
I'm the one who should ask you.
I had to do it.
You have to help me.
OK?
I'm asking you, "Are you ok?"
Do I have to kill them?
Why do you have to waste your time?
Let them kill each other.
Are you sure about this?
Some cases are not in our role.
We only have a duty to
keep the eyes on them.
Perhaps, The Gang of Cherry wouldn't
suit for here anymore. Agree?
It's a very sunny day.
Do you like it?
She walks through this way alone.
It is reflectively desolated.
Follow her, keep follow her.
What a beating heart!
She is wearing slutty appearance.
That's making me horny.
Follow her without missing sight.
Want to fuck her.
Restrain myself, Restrain myself...
I can't stand. I can't stand...
This shall be raping.
You shall be raped.
Seeing you makes me want to rape.
You deserve to be raped.
This shall be raping.
You shall be raped.
Seeing you makes me want to rape.
You deserve to be raped.
Fucked up!
The body is gone.
Besides that motherfucker,
anyone else went into the building?
No.
You go take care of the other body,
So we don't waste our time.
Take this. In case you need it.
For what?
So you can trust me.
What about you?
I'll take care of the other body.
No.
You gotta go back to the building.
What the fuck are you waiting for?
Shoot!
You take one. I take one.
Let it out,
So we can go away together.
Because you're like this,
You have to live in pain.
Shoot!
Who's going away with you?
Have I said that?
When did I say that?
You don't have the guts to shoot me.
How do you know?
Because it's too hard for you.
You and I no longer owe each other.
And you two can sort it out by yourselves.
Let's go that way.
Wait for me here.
Got it?
Stay here.
You wanna stay with me?
Stick out your tonque.
Behave!
Lie down.
Sit.
Sit down!
You wanna stay with me, right?
Help me.
I'm sorry.