Higher...
Higher.
What?
Who is it?
Let go of me!
Where... where am I?
Hey!
You're alive.
Let me make you feel alive.
《Dangerous Drugs of Sex》
Easy. You have to relax.
Stop
I'm not gonna stop.
Stop!
I said I won't stop.
I'm gonna find you all your best spots.
Stop! It's itchy!
Stop, you freak...
Fre...
Stop! Freak!
Freak!
Freak... Freak...
Freak! Freak! Freak!
Ah... freak...
Freak...
That's all you have to say?
Then I'm gonna continue.
No... Ah... I've to go to toilet.
Please let me go to toilet.
Liar.
You see, there's nothing in your bladder.
What?
I took a shower for you when you passed out.
I got everything out of you.
Here too.
Nothing inside.
You're just empty now.
Your life is mine now.
You don't have to understand.
Just take in everything i give you.
What's that?
Enemagra.
It's a great invention by a urologist.
Very effective for stimulating prostate.
See... you're getting hard.
I'm... not...
It's in your instinct...
You want to live...
So hot... you can't escape from such ecstacy
because you can't move, huh?
Don't worry, you'll have so many
chances to get there again.
So... hot...
Pull it... pull it out!
I'm not gonna run... I'm not gonna run!
I'll die...
I'll die... I'm gonna die...
You're living your moment!
No, no... no...
Mr. Katsuragi...
Chief?
It's dream...
You're too tired.
Sorry. You finished?
Yeah.
You stayed up late again yesterday,
didn't you?
You should take some rest.
You're gonna do it for me?
I can't!
I'm gonna have my rest after this is done.
There might already be an answer for you.
Boss' looking for you.
The proposal passed.
Really?
You did a great job.
Thank you very much.
I should be the one saying thank you.
This is a big event since foundation.
Leader of this project...
can you do it?
It's my pleasure.
Don't feel too good about yourself yet.
You can go even higher.
I see.
What is it, Mom?
What happened?
Just we haven't been eating with you
for a long time.
I want it to be nice.
Sorry, I have been busy.
Don't push yourself too hard.
It's all nothing if you died.
Don't say that!
Come on, sit.
Right, before dinner,
I want you to have this.
I got a bonus.
You two should go on a travel sometimes.
What are you talking about, so much!?
Just take it.
Thank you, Makoto.
You're welcome.
I should be the one thanking you having me.
That's enough.
Sake.
Ok.
It feels like a dream, haha.
Dream.
It's a dream.
It's not a dream.
Morning.
Didn't we say you can't run?
Nutrition and water needed for a day.
And vitamin.
Who's gonna...
You think it's poison?
Starved to death is very painful, I tell you.
Much more painful than
jumping down from a building.
I'm not going to kill you.
My job is to save people.
No...
It's from you Dad.
He's called several times.
What is it?
They are coming back from Okinawa today.
The trip you gave them as a gift?
You're such a good son.
I promised to pick them up at the airport.
But you promised you will stay the night.
Sorry, I forgot.
"Are you busy at work?"
"We can take taxi ourselves.
You don't have to come."
They said.
Oh I fucked up.
You bad son.
Just stay the night with me.
Sorry.
Hey, don't run.
My name is Katsuragi.
Please follow me.
The taxi ran into a truck.
When arrived at the hospital,
they've already...
Are you okay, Mr. Katsuragi?
Breathe slowly.
My... it's all my fault....
My fault.
My...
Calmer after eating, right?
You had some sleep, huh?
What?
You haven't ejaculated, right?
You have to at least ejaculate once...
Relax.
Hey, there's no way to put it in...
How is it? Feel good?
No... how can it feel good...
You sure? Just like that..
If I stop here, it will feel like
burning down here, no?
No...
I heard that.
You want to shoot... just a little bit more...
Deeper... you want to shoot...
You want to shoot...
Your waist is shaking.
See.
Feels good, huh?
No... my nipples...
Want to shoot?
Go ahead.
It's no good to hold it
No... I can't like this...
Yeah? This is not enough?
You're shaking yourself.
Coming... it's coming...
It's out...
One more.
Please stop.
Shut up.
I can't sell you anymore.
Huh?
Please don't move.
Please go home.
Hey, where's my wallet?
There.
Mr. Katsuragi?
Don't take it the wrong way.
We were just having dinner together.
I couldn't recognize you.
You've changed a lot, Mr. Katsuragi.
I've called you many times.
It's too over absent without
notice for over a month.
You should come to the office.
They say you'll get your severance.
Weird... my hair's longer...
It dosn't matter anymore.
You are to achieve higher.
Higher...
Higher..
Who is it...
You want to die that bad?
I want to die.
If you're throwing your life away,
how about give it to me.
You're clean now.
Good view.
Don't struggle...
you're gonna hurt your knees.
Leave me alone! Hey!
Told you not to move.
Stop.
Hey, stop.
This is... the arteria carotis.
Good..nice boy.
You're turing into a good man.
That's enough. Let me go.
Here too.
It might hurt you if you keep moving.
All clean.
Embarrassed?
We have to clean inside too.
No... ah...
One is not enough?
It's standing up again.
You're gifted.
Try have a orgasm with back here.
No...
Here too?
Come on, a little bit more.
I... I...
See, you can do it.
You can take it out...
Now that we're in the bathroom,
get it all out.
It's done. Stop.
What? No, see it's coming.
It's coming.
What's coming?
See, refreshed, right?
Ecstacy acquired from being played,
nontop unconscious pleasure...
I... No... No...
I couldn't think at all.
I could only embrace everything
he did to my body.
Stop...
Want more?
Even so, my instinct told me to fight back.
Stop...
To reject as I am a man...
I was forced to bear this fear and ecstacy.
Struggle between life and death.
Why am I alive?
Why not let me die...
No, you have to eat it all.
You're awake, right?
Do it if you want to.
Taking life from the other,
or from yourself,
God is not going to stop you.
Do it.
Stop.
Why are you doing this?
Who knows?
Then why do you want to die?
Tell me.
I... have nothing...
It's all my fault... to loose everything.
It's not a reason.
What?
You think your death can bring them back?
What do you know!
I know everything.
What?
I'm the same.
What's that supposed to mean?
Drink it and you can die easily.
You decide.
How is he?
Visceral rupture by falling
when working at height.
It&s critical.
Operation room ready?
On the way.
Am I gonna die?
You want to live?
I have kids... I don't wanna die...
Then I'm not loosing you.
Let's get started.
-Yes. -Yes.
Suction.
On it.
Doctor.
It's ok. He's fighting.
It' ok.
It' ok...
-Defibrillator. -Here.
Damn.
Please.
Why?
Doctor.
Thank you so much.
I'm very sorry. I've done everything I could.
Why?
Why... do lives pass away?
You didn't drink it?
It's just normal water.
I thought you wanted to die.
You... it's you...
I... I what?
Don't laugh.
You're hard.
You were going to say that
I made your body this way?
It's your purpose!
Don't laugh!
It's what you did
making my body...
Yes.
S... Stop
Stop.
Feeling good? You're so hard.
You want it, don't you?
You don't want it? Then bite me.
Come on, come on, you hate me, don't you?
I can die for you.
Bite!
Hey, come on, do it!
It's twitching inside.
So hot, you're still alive...
You're living out the best of you...
So... so hot...
What are you laughing at...
I will talk to the Doctor.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Can I help you?
No, sorry.
Okay.
You're here to jump again?
You...
You're free now.
You're so ruined
if I sue you for what you did.
You wish to ruin me?
Someone like you trying to
take his own life?
I didn't get your name.
That's right... I'm Ryuji Yoden. You?
I'm...
Makoto Katsuragi. I know.
This hospital...
You should remember,
This is where we first met.
Sorry.
They came in with no vital signs.
Don't hate me.
It's not anyone's fault, nor yours.
You hungry?
It's my treat. What do you want to eat?
Where do you want to go next?
Look ahead when driving.
Okay.
There can be an accident.
You're right.
I met you here before.
The secone coincidence.
All me...
You're not the only one
loosing important ones.
What?
So alike.
Sorry.
Go ahead, Doctor Genius.
Don't laugh at me.
I'm envying you.
I envy you can save lives.
Our work fights with death a lot.
And I have my way of doing it
as a emergency physician.
But he works in the hospice. To him,
there's even no chance to fight.
The unsavable lives had been eating him up.
I didn't notice his condition.
I thought you quit.
What?
Cigarette.
I forgot.
It's not your fault.
Yeah.
How about take some rest?
Yoden.
Can you come to my place tonight?
Fuck me, all you can.
It's rare to hear something like from you.
Weird?
Weird.
That's right.
Sorry, I'm on duty tonight.
Okay.
I'll go tomorrow.
You don't have to say that.
I want to.
The hospital was busy that night.
I saved three person from dying that night.
But,
I couldn't save the most important one.
All I felt was anger.
To him, and to myself.
This was his, fentanyl.
A pain killer hundred times powerful
than Morphine.
Strong poison.
I was looking a place to die with this.
Then,
I saw you, for the third time.
Three coincidence. I told myself
I have to catch this guy.
I won't let go.
A guy so much like him
is to die in front of me.
I can't let it happen.
I have to bury the idea of being alive
into his head with the most humiliating way.
I want to implant the living instinct
into his mind.
This is a powerful drug to save lives.
Drug. That's how you want to do it?
You remember what you said to me
at the beginning?
What?
Freak.
Freak, that's it.
Willing to accept someone like me,
I take it you're one of us.
Stop it.
I'll stop.
Your life is no longer mine.
Do whatever you want.
How can you say that...
You will live no matter what.
I...
I can do whatever I want, right?
Give me your life.
What are you going to do to me?
What should I do?
Don't act as if you knew.
Ah... no.
You're about to?
You remember, right?
You can do whateve you want. It's all yours.
I'm not him.
I'm... Makoto Katsuragi.
Are you alive?
Alive.