...happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Chava.
-Blow them out!
-Ask for a wish, dear.
Blow out the candles!
-Oh!
-Bravo!
Blow harder!
There! That's it!
There, there.
That's cheating!
These evil candles,
they never blow out.
The candle blows out when
you're sure about your wish.
But you have to bite the cake first.
Right! Bite the cake, bite it!
No, no.
¡Bravo!
-No, sit down!
-Don't do it!
¡Wow!
Excellent.
-I hope this one wakes you up.
-Put that down.
Mom.
Hello.
What's up?
Right, as usual.
You always come up with some excuse.
Fine, then.
That creep will never change.
-Chava, he's your dad.
-That's how I know.
He either misses his flight
or crashes into a truck.
Maybe it's an aphrodisiac.
-I told you to leave it alone.
-What a temper!
I mean it when I say
you could use a girlfriend.
TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF
Did you like the present?
Hey.
Hi, Chava.
-How are you?
-Fine.
-What's this?
-It's our 4-month anniversary.
-Right, "shweetie"?
-"Yesh".
There you go again.
Quit showing off.
Why? You can have Chava.
Now that sexual diversity
is in style.
No, no way, dude, I respect all that,
but I'm totally into women.
-Oh, please!
-And I can prove it.
How can you prove it?
In that case let's do this.
This year you have to get a girlfriend.
Is that a challenge?
-Yes.
-You're on.
-What about you, Chava?
-You accept the challenge too?
Chava wants a girlfriend!
Okay, let's go to class.
This is the last topic that will be
on the test next week.
Remember it's an important
percentage of your final grade.
No, Mrs. Bertha.
Quiet! Who remembers the difference
between a function and an equation?
What have I told you
about those devices?
Put them away, please.
Everybody.
-Ramón?
-Mrs. Bertha,
I know the answer, but...
Ramón isn't inspired today.
HI HANDSOME :)
Hannah, please
Last class we learned that a function
can be expressed as an equation,
but not always vice-versa.
WHO ARE YOU?
Very good. Today we'll talk about...
YOUR SECRET ADMIRER.
polinominal functions.
Chava. Chava.
Next time I see your
cell phone, you won't get it back
until the end of the semester.
Is that clear?
Yes, Mrs. Bertha.
That goes for all of you.
Well, that's all for today.
Study up. Especially you, Ramón.
You know I love flunking you.
Remember that.
-Yes, teacher.
-Goodbye.
Hold on. Hey. Was it you guys?
Us? What are you talking about?
What the hell, Chava,
you were spacing out.
I'm fine. Later.
Move, asshole.
See you around, gorgeous.
GIVE ME A CLUE?
Come on, Chava. Glide.
Move, Chava. Keep going. Be consistent.
Let's go!
Where's your endurance?
Coach, give me a minute. I'm tired.
No. You have thirty seconds.
Very good, Carlos,
but don't slam the water.
Soft strokes, remember.
otherwise the water will hold you back.
Okay? Good.
Come on, Chava! Time's up.
Happy birthday.
Look at you, you're all grown up.
Sorry I couldn't be here.
There were issues at the site,
and work is a priority.
One day you'll understand.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Dinner's ready.
Bring the sauces please, Chava.
You still haven't fixed that faucet.
I'll fix it over the weekend.
Are you going to be here?
Well, if I'm not here
you can fix it yourself,
you're old enough.
You haven't taught me how.
Nobody taught me, I learned by myself.
Finish your dinner.
I lost my appetite.
AT LEAST TELL ME YOUR NAME.
THEY CALL ME LITTLE WITCH.
LITTLE WITCH...
COME ON... TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF.
JUST ASK...
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
I knew you'd be here.
Your present.
OUR SONG
The toy car was a joke.
Remember I used to bring you here?
That's why I like coming.
We used to have picnics.
Cassette player, music,
we'd sing and dance.
I never understood
why you liked
coming here more than the park.
Back then everything was right, Dad.
You spent time at home.
Mom seemed happy.
Now I'm not so sure anymore.
The things you come up with.
Who were you texting?
-Some girlfriend, I suppose?
-No, no.
Busted, busted.
Let's go to class, dude!
-Why are you so concentrated?
-Give it back.
What's all this?
Damn you, Chava.
Why didn't you say anything?
I have no idea who she is, dude.
-Little Witch.
-Buddy,
he's going to win the bet, man.
Only if he finds out who it is.
Do you know?
Zilch. It's nobody.
You're fucking kidding me, Chavita!
What if it's her?
It can't be her.
You're just jealous.
Why not? He's tall and handsome.
Chavita. If it's her, you're gonna
totally win the bet. Look at her.
But how can we find out?
-Inviting her to the party Friday?
-Good idea.
Tell her to meet you at a certain time
and mystery solved.
That's good, "shweetie".
Go ahead and write to her: "Babe..."
I'm not calling her Babe.
-What should we say?
-"What are you doing on Friday?"
We have that party, remember?
-Little Witch, Fran.
-Right!
"Hi, Little Witch... I have an idea.".
"What are you doing on Friday?"
-Why are you late, Chava?
-Sorry, Coach.
Let's do this, people!
Glide, come on.
Good!
Come on, Chava!
YOU DIDN'T ANSWER
I WANT TO INVITE YOU TO A PARTY.
Let's see.
-What are you wearing?
-Hm.
Let's do this, folks!
The drinks are here.
-Ready?
-Ready.
This one's mine.
-Okay. Cheers, guys.
-Cheers!
Ah!
-Let's dance, "shweetie"?
-"Yesh".
So? Are you ready?
I'm shitting myself.
Literally?
No, dude.
I mean I'm nervous, that's all.
It would be gross if you
were actually shitting yourself.
What time did you tell her?
At ten. I said I'd wait at the door.
-Shit, it's almost time!
-Right.
-One more shot?
-Let's down it.
-Here, Chavita.
-You were thirsty!
In a bad way, buddy.
I love this song. We have to dance.
-Come dance, Chava.
-I'll be right there.
Fran, Fran, Fran...!
Are you expecting someone?
Yes.
I'm Carlos.
We practice swimming together.
I'm Salvador.
-Chava, everyone calls me Chava.
-Yes, I know.
Marco, the coach,
is always yelling your name.
"Faster, Chava! You can do it, Chava!"
Well, good luck with that.
I GUESS YOU'RE NOT COMING.
What's up, Chava?
She didn't come.
Take it easy, you don't drink.
Chava, Chava.
Where are you going, dude?
Why didn't you come?
-Excuse me?
-We said we'd meet at ten.
You stood me up really bad.
Damn witch!
-You're the damn witch!
-What did you call me?
You know who you are,
stop fucking around.
I don't know what you mean.
My secret admirer?
Are you all right, Chava?
What happened, man?
-Let's go to the bathroom.
-Chava.
Are you all right, Chava?
It wasn't her.
I'm such an idiot!
You were right, Fran.
Yeah dude, but you didn't have to go
and make a fool of yourself.
You could have been more discreet.
Well, it's the truth.
Are you my friends?
I need to be by myself, please.
See you upstairs.
I'd never seen you like this.
I'm not drunk, Dad.
Right.
Look.
You left it last time.
I started singing...
Bye-bye, Miss American Pie
Drove my Chevy to the levee
But the levee was dry
Them good old boys
were drinking whiskey and rye
Singing,
"This'll be the day that I die"
This will be the day that I die
Now for ten years
we've been on our own
And moss grows fat on a rolling stone
But that's not how it used to be
That's enough.
When the jester sang
for the King and Queen
In a coat he borrowed from James Dean
#And a voice
that came from you and me#
Oh and while the King
was looking down
The jester stole his...
Chava, Chava. That's enough.
Enough, hey.
No verdict was returned...
It seems your adolescent rebelliousness
came a little late, right?
No way.
Hand me the jack and the rod, please.
Jack and rod.
Perfect.
Shine the light here.
Bring the spare tire.
MESSAGE FROM LITTLE WITCH:
Are we eating together on Tuesday?
I love you.
You look like you saw a ghost.
Don't tell me you're tired,
you didn't do anything.
Thanks. Let's go.
There goes the vomit guy!
The puker! What an asshole.
"You're the damn witch".
Chava.
Chava... Chava.
Time's up.
I need your test.
Damn Witch! You're the damn witch!
What did you call me?
My secret admirer?
Fucking shit.
Wanna ride?
No, thanks.
I don't bite, man.
-If you want to get wet, fine.
-All right!
Excuse the mess.
Don't worry about it.
Do you drive by the loop?
No, but I can change my route.
Sure?
So, how are you?
-Fine.
-No, I mean really.
I'm asking because
of the video and the memes.
I haven't seen any of it.
What's up with that?
You have a secret admirer?
Don't be like that.
I'm giving you a ride.
At least tell me the whole story.
-You're charging for the favor?
-Sure.
Everything in life has a price, Chava.
Relax, dude. I'm joking.
But I do want to know.
Tell you what, how about
you tell me everything over a beer?
Cool, isn't it?
That's my grandmother.
I live here with her.
You haven't changed.
I get that a lot.
Beer, or should I make
a cup a of tea
and show you my family photo albums?
Whatever you want.
Don't be an idiot.
I'll hand you a beer.
So you think your secret admirer
is your dad's lover?
How else would you explain he got
a message from her
agreeing to eat together?
I don't know.
Maybe it's a different Little Witch.
That's a hell of a coincidence.
Actually, it is very weird.
I'll help you, if you want.
How?
We can follow your dad
and catch him red-handed.
Om, shanti, shanti.
Shanti, shanti... shanti...
Since when do you meditate?
Your mom is teaching me.
-Join us.
-I have homework.
Maybe tomorrow then.
No, I can't tomorrow.
-Why not?
-I have a trip.
-Again?
-I have to supervise the construction.
You know how it is.
Shit, Chava.
-Let me see.
-You always get A.
The thing with your secret admirer
is getting out of control, dude.
-If you only knew.
-What?
Nothing. I mean,
it really is bothering me.
Speak of the devil.
Chava, don't make another scene.
What's he doing?
Mariana.
Sorry about the party.
I was wasted and someone
played a trick on me.
I stupidly thought it was you.
"I'm Chava, can I vomit on you?"
It's all right.
I freaked out when you puked.
I confess that I think the thing
about a secret admirer is sweet.
But no problem. Seriously.
Thanks.
Hey.
You should at least ask me out
for coffee so I will forgive you.
Are you kidding me?
Text me.
Yes.
What was that?
-No way, Mariana?
-Yes, dude.
No way! Mariana? Shit yeah.
What did you say to her?
What time are they meeting?
I don't know.
The message only said
they would eat together.
Did you know penguins choose
one single mate for their lifetime?
Really?
Do you have a girlfriend?
You're joking, aren't you?
I'm gay.
Gay, homosexual, queer.
What about you?
Me?
There he is.
I told you! That son of a bitch!
Calm down.
What's her number?
Hello? Hello?
-I have to go in.
-No, hang on.
We'll follow them when they come out.
So this is their little love den.
Sorry.
What a son of a bitch!
Hey, I apologized.
No, not you. Him.
Now I understand all those trips
and his bullshit lectures.
The point here is what's
the deal with that damn Little Witch?
She bewitched the dad,
what does she want with the son?
Let's go.
-What are you gonna do?
-I don't know.
Chava.
What's going on with you?
Finals are coming up.
Don't fall short.
Yes, Mrs. Bertha.
I think he's gonna beat you.
Are you kidding, Hugo?
You're still betting?
Hey.
Do you have a moment
to talk about God?
Or to read a brochure,
or to buy a Bible?
Uh...
You seem worried.
If it's about sex before marriage,
I've been through that.
Here's our brochure.
-I'll read it later.
-Come to an assembly.
-The first one is free.
-No.
-It isn't free?
I said no, thank--
Chava?
What are you doing here?
Hello, Little Witch.
What the hell do you want?
You're fucking the dad
and hitting on the son too?
-You don't know what you're saying.
-I don't?
Álvaro? Sound familiar?
Álvaro...
...is my dad.
I'm your sister.
Vanessa.
What?
Uh, yes.
No.
CAN WE HANG OUT?
COME OVER.
That chick is fucking nuts.
Flirting with her half brother.
What about your dad?
He's the biggest son of a bitch.
No.
Carlos, don't get confused.
I'm not like you.
Like me?
I see.
Everything all right?
I'M SORRY, CHAVA.
I went over last night...
-I don't know where it is.
-We have Chemistry now.
I don't know where I put it.
Mariana?
Chava. Hi.
Do you have class?
Yes. Why?
I thought we could
go get something to drink.
Right now?
Why not?
Okay, let's go.
So? Who was your secret admirer?
Nobody. It was a joke my mentally
challenged friends played on me.
Can I tell you a secret?
I've been watching you for a while.
That's how I know you're different.
You have my number.
Boo!
What do you want?
I texted you and you didn't reply,
so my only option
was coming to see you.
Chava! Chava, let me explain please.
Coffee and a slice of pie, please.
Coffee and pie. For you?
The same.
-What kind of pie?
-Lime
Lime, good. Coming up.
You look so much like Dad.
I only found out recently.
I got angry, very angry,
and started investigating your family.
I got your number
and decided to approach you.
So I would tell you everything?
At first, yes.
I wanted to know more.
Where you lived, how you lived.
I always went to public schools.
I never had any luxuries.
I was envious.
Very envious.
But then I liked talking to you.
Deep down I always
wanted to have a brother.
Two pies.
Does your mom know?
No.
I guess she suspects.
Dad spends very little time with us.
One week with us and three weeks
away because he's working...
And it's always been that way.
What about... your mom?
No.
-Sorry.
-Wait, wait.
Will I see you again?
Bye.
Can I have milk, please?
Sure.
Chava. Chava, What the hell, dude?
I hardly see you anymore.
-Are you all right?
-Yes, I'm fine..
Let's go for some wings.
I can't. I have a swimming competition.
Well, good luck with that.
Some other time.
Hi. Hi, Chava.
Mariana.
These are Hannah, Hugo and Fran.
Nice meeting you.
May I steal him for a minute?
Sure. He's all yours.
What's up?
I thought you would write to me.
Yes, sorry.
I've got a lot on my mind,
but I promise to make it up to you.
-Friday?
-Okay.
-It's a fact, then?
-Yes, you have my word.
Okay.
No fucking way.
So it's a tie, Chava?
I don't think so. Not yet.
Who would have thought, Chavita?
You're a Casanova.
Stop it.
Okay, guys.
The first round will be duels.
One against the other.
The pair with the same number
are rivals.
Okay, who has number 1?
Okay. Who else?
Fine, first pair. Get in the water.
Let's go! Move it, people.
The rest of you continue warming up.
Let's go!
Ready...
Come on, come on!
Good, Carlos. Very good.
Well done, Carlos.
All right, next pair.
Number two.
Hey.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Sorry if I made you feel uncomfortable
the other night. I didn't mean to.
See you tomorrow, Martínez!
Hey, I've been thinking.
I think you have to tell your mom.
Otherwise you would
become an accomplice.
Accomplices are just as guilty
as offenders, or something like that.
I think it would destroy my mom.
It will hurt more if she finds out
you knew and didn't tell her.
Why are you charging me
for the wings? We're buddies.
Hey. You're waiting for me?
Of course, we have to celebrate.
-But I lost.
-No.
You came in second place.
It wasn't that bad.
Dude, we ate all the wings.
You took too long.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Let's go.
-Chava the champ!
-I came in second.
-It's a Rubik cube, Fran.
-I've never solved it.
Who is it?
Hi.
I wasn't satisfied
with your answer yesterday,
so I took the liberty
of coming to see you.
By the way, I'm Vanessa.
Everybody calls me Little Witch
because I can see the future.
I actually saw Chava.
Take that expression off your faces,
it looks you saw a ghost.
-You want a ride?
-No. They're on the school bus.
I'll take you. Let's go.
We can all fit in my Beetle.
Let's go.
-Let's?
-Let's.
So, he showed up at my place
and it turns out that Chava and I
are... siblings.
Half.
Uh, half siblings.
Well, that's cool, isn't it?
I mean, finding out you have a sibling.
Isn't it?
-Well, let's go.
-Let's.
You know what?
That's okay,
we'll go on the school bus.
I can take you, seriously.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
Thanks.
Don't say anything,
I'll tell you about it later.
-Fine.
-Yeah, no problem.
Well, it was a pleasure
meeting you, Little Witch.
You too.
-Anything you need, huh?
-Thanks.
Love your hair.
Fran?
Fra-Fran, right. F-r-a-n.
-Fran.
Yeah, cool.
-Bye.
Bye.
-Your carriage, sir.
-What was that all about?
-What?
-You can't just show up and act
like we're one big, happy family.
I don't know you,
and you don't know me.
Give me some space.
Everything all right?
Wanna join me?
No, I don't like it.
You should try
just to spend more time
with your mother.
Mom, are you happy?
Sure. Can't you tell?
No, it's a serious question.
Are you happy with Dad?
I already said yes.
Dad has another family.
Chava...
Mom, I'm serious. I saw him.
I don't want to talk about it, Chava.
Respect that.
I made my decision a long time ago.
Now you can make your own.
Dad?
I thought you were on a trip.
Chava.
Yes, but I just got back today.
I'm here helping a friend.
He has a problem.
He lives here.
What are you doing around here?
Same thing. Going to a friend's house.
I'd give you a ride but
I don't know how long this will take.
That's okay, I'll wait for you.
That way I can meet your friends.
You haven't introduced us.
Álvaro! Is the bread here?
Hi.
Who is this kid?
I'm Salvador. His son.
Is dinner ready?
No.
It wasn't supposed
to be like this, Chava.
You did the same thing to me.
Go away. Just go.
I knew it, I knew it.
Dad?
-Dad?
-Go.
I'll explain it to you later.
Please don't say anything
to your mother.
I FUCKED UP
WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE.
LET'S GO AWAY! PACK A SMALL BAG.
MEET ME TOMORROW AT THE GATE...
Aren't you telling me
where we're going?
You're so impatient.
You're like a little boy, dude.
-To a wedding.
-On a Friday?
Maybe it was cheaper.
-We have to change.
-What?
Try this on.
-Here?
-Yeah.
Wow.
Charlie.
Congratulations.
I'm glad you made it.
Chava! what a surprise.
Bruno, honey, come.
These are my students.
-Chava and Charlie.
-Hi, it's a pleasure.
I'm so glad you came.
Marco, Bruno.
Sorry for interrupting, we're all set.
-Come please?
-Yes.
See you later, you two hurry up.
-Wow.
-What the hell, why didn't you tell me?
I said we were going
to a friend's wedding. I didn't lie.
-No, but it's our coach.
-Mhm.
-and it's a gay wedding.
-What's the big deal?
Come on.
MISSED MESSAGES
-Oh! Let's dance, come on.
-I'll be right there.
-Come on.
-I'm coming.
-Promise.
-Okay, see you later.
-No.
-Come dance.
Hey.
Are you all right?
I'm not sure.
-Because of what happened?
-No.
Well, yeah. Sort of.
I don't know.
Everything suddenly changed.
I have a half sister,
I don't know my dad anymore,
and worst of all, I don't know myself.
Discovery.
That's what life is all about, Chava.
Sometimes it's for the best,
sometimes it's not.
This is only the beginning.
It's not that I'm emotional
over another sunrise,
but it's the first one
that you spend with me.
I don't want to see
the sunrise by myself ever again.
Alone it has no flair or pleasure.
One, two, three!
When you set your eyes on me
I experience adventures
without going anywhere.
I can't stop laughing
when I look at you
because I know
it was your kiss that I saw.
Ask me for whatever you want,
I'll say yes.
Ask me for nonsense,
but never,
never go away
I have a right to be happy.
Never go far.
If you go
it would be too much for me.
Where are you going?
Will you be back?
Say you'll take me too
Love me, kiss me.
Leave your trace on me at dawn...
-No.
-It was this one.
You're going to laugh,
but I've never changed a tire.
We need a jack...
and a lug "knot".
-You have no idea, do you?
-I don't.
Let's look it up.
Thank God for the 21st century.
Fucking shit, dude.
One of the coaches
married his boyfriend.
-No way, he's a faggot?
-Sure, didn't you know?
You can tell he's a fairy.
That's true.
He's always hanging out with Carlos.
They say queers stick together.
-Those faggots.
-Fucking gross.
I know, it's disgusting.
Chava.
You owe us an explanation, dude.
I know.
We've been your friends
for a helluva long time.
That's what friends are for,
-to lean on.
-What the hell?
What the hell, Chava? You stood me up.
If you think I'm going to chase you,
you're fucking stupid.
Chava.
You wanna watch a movie
or something? What's wrong?
Chava, tell us what's going on.
-What's the matter?
-You changed.
That's enough!
You guys say you're my friends
but I can never speak
to one of you privately.
You're like a combo.
And you Fran,
you're always screwing with me.
It seems all you care about
is the damn bet.
How fucking selfish.
And you? What do you want?
You take me to a gay wedding
and then you expect us to paint
the world in rainbow colors?
Or organize a gay pride parade?
No, Carlos. I'm not like you.
I'm not a faggot!
You're an asshole!
You really are an ass, Chava.
#I'M NOT A FAGGOT
Hi there.
How's school?
Fine.
How's your sweetheart?
What?
Why haven't you told me?
The other day I caught him
texting his girlfriend.
I'm gay.
No way, you're not gay.
Yes. Gay.
Homosexual, queer...
-Don't joke about this.
-I'm not joking, Mom.
Didn't you hear me?
-I'm gay.
-No, son. You're not gay.
You're confused.
Are you just saying it for revenge...?
Revenge for what, Dad?
I don't-- I don't know.
For what happened on your birthday.
You're not that way.
Gay people suffer a lot.
They're beaten,
discriminated, and rejected.
You don't want that for yourself.
It's not that I want it,
it's the way I am.
What do you prefer?
For me to live my life pretending
I'm something I'm not?
A person I'm not?
No, Dad.
You and I are different that way.
You didn't catch me
texting a girlfriend.
It was your daughter trying
to make sense of your double life.
No, no, Mom, don't cry.
You knew and decided to keep quiet.
You told me to make my own decision.
Today I'm deciding to stop this farce.
What do you want?
Can we talk?
Come in, it's open.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to say all that.
I know I screwed up.
I told my parents.
What?
That you are indeed like me?
That you are indeed a faggot?
I'm glad you finally accepted it.
One day you offend me in front
of your friends,
and then you want the world
to be rainbow colored.
No, Chava.
That's not the way it works.
I like you... I like you a lot.
But you're in a different place.
You're barely discovering yourself,
accepting yourself,
and that's fine.
But I've been through that
and I know what it means.
If one day you
need a shoulder to cry on
or someone to talk to,
I'll be here.
But only as a friend.
Because it's not easy, Chava.
Not easy at all.
Goodbye.
I will be quiet for a few days
I'll stay away from your name
and from my artillery
I'll embrace the horizon
and I will forget
I will learn to forget
If he truly loves you
let him sing for you
And if he couldn't love you
let him cry for you
May someone steal your heart away
without a warning,
To make you understand
of miracles and of the sea
I will be quiet for a few days,
I'll stay away from your name
and from my artillery
I'll embrace the horizon
and I will forget
I will learn to forget
PLEASE COME.
I'M ON THE ROOFTOP
OF 32 ARCHIMEDES AVE.
I will learn to forget
Everything's gone to shit.
I can't go home,
my friends hate me,
and the dude I like
told me to go to hell.
It was all my fault.
I confronted Dad.
He isn't with us anymore.
Sorry.
I was out of control, I was furious.
Maybe things happen for a reason.
I never had the balls
to tell the truth.
Instead of that, I acted like a child
and made up this stupid
secret admirer diversion.
And we know how that went.
Maybe things happen for a reason.
Good morning.
Sorry, it's getting late.
But relax.
Don't rush.
Did you know penguins choose
one single mate for their lifetime?
No.
I didn't know that,
"Mister Discovery Channel".
Take it.
-Really?
-Sure.
A gift from your half sister.
Thanks.
Thanks for everything.
I'm here for you.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
Looking good, Hannah!
Apologize to her, jerk.
Or else?
You'll vomit on me, faggot?
-If I have to.
-"If I have to".
What happened?
What happened? Hannah won't tell me.
Cha-Chava.
I told you to apologize to her.
I'm not going to, queer.
Chava...
Chava.
Thanks.
That's what friends are for.
Sorry.
For what I said.
-For being distant, for what I did.
-It's okay.
Really, we all have
our bad moments, okay?
That jerk is getting expelled.
You're so brave, man.
Get over here, Chava.
SORRY AGAIN!
32 ARCHIMEDES AVE.
TONIGHT AT 7 P.M.
Chava.
Come.
Why, Mom?
Why didn't you ever say anything?
For you.
-Oh.
-I didn't want to put you through this.
-Don't use me as an excuse.
-No, Chava, it isn't an excuse.
It's the truth.
But here I am now...
...facing you
and asking you to forgive me.
I thought you wouldn't come.
Here I am.
Now what?
I don't know, Dad.
I don't know you.
I don't know who you are.
Please...
...tell me about yourself.
It seems Chavita won the bet
one to zero.
No. Not yet, Fran.
FOR MY FATHER...
WHO LEFT BEFORE HE WAS ABLE
TO TELL ME ABOUT HIMSELF